Herb Staehr Collection ARC.0029
Library and Archives
- Series VI: Concert, Studio, and Television Recordings [RESTRICTED], circa 1960s-2000s
  - Subseries 2: DVD-Video, circa 1960s-2000s
    - Clapton, Eric
      - Hong Kong, China, 2007 January 17 (Box 9, Object 143)
      - Melbourne, Australia, 2007 February 7 (Box 9, Object 144-145)
      - Good Morning America with John Mayer, 2007 July 20 (Box 9, Object 146)
      - Crossroads Festival, Toyota Park, Bridgeport, Illinois, 2007 July 28 (Box 9, Object 147-149)
      - Today Show, 2007 October 9 (Box 9, Object 150)
      - Larry King Live; Weekend Today Show, 2007 October 12-2007 October 13 (Box 9, Object 151)
      - Promo compile, undated (Box 9, Object 152-153)
    - Climax Blues Band: Gut Opherdike, Germany; Marquee Club, London, England, 1983-1984 (Box 9, Object 154)
    - Cocker, Joe
      - Metropol, Berlin, Germany; Vancouver, British Columbia, Canada, 1980 October 31, 1981 (Box 9, Object 155)
      - Live in Calgary, Alberta, Canada, 1981 May (Box 9, Object 156)
      - Loreley, Germany; Westfalenhalle, Dortmund, Germany, 1983 August 20, 1984 June 23 (Box 9, Object 157)
      - Ohne Filter Extra, 1988 (Box 9, Object 158)
      - Bosenbachstadion, St. Wendel, Germany, 1989 June 23 (Box 9, Object 159)
      - Tonight Show Starring Johnny Carson; Rock in Rio II; Guitar Legends Concert, Seville, Spain, 1990-1991 (Box 9, Object 160)
      - PBS Center Stage; Joe Cocker: Have a Little Faith -- 50th birthday profile [German television], 1992, 1994 (Box 9, Object 161)
      - Woodstock '94; Behind the Music, 1994, 1998 (Box 9, Object 162)
      - Have a Little Faith [A&E profile]; Austin City Limits, 1994, 2001 (Box 9, Object 163)
    - Collins, Albert: Austin City Limits, 1992 (Box 7, Object 142)
    - Cray, Robert
      - Montreux, Switzerland; Washington, D.C. [private], 1986 July 9, 1986 (Box 9, Object 164)
      - Various including Saturday Night Live, Ohne Filter Extra [German television], Arsenio Hall Show, 1987-1989 (Box 9, Object 165)
      - Austin City Limits; Schlacthof, Munich, Germany; New Orleans with John Lee Hooker, 1989, 1991 (Box 10, Object 1)
      - Paul Mason Festival, San Francisco, California, 1991 July 27 (Box 10, Object 2)
    - Cream
      - Royal Albert Hall, London, England [beta tape version and BBC-4 rebroadcast], 1968 November 26, 2005 April 29 (Box 10, Object 3-5)
      - Various including U.S. Tour home movies, Smotehrs Brothers Comedy Hour, Eric Clapton and Jack Bruce reunion, 1968, 1987-1993 (Box 10, Object 6)
      - Television appearances including Gonks Go Beat with Ginger Baker [on Bobby Darin DVD], 1965 and undated (Box 10, Object 30)
      - Rock and Roll Hall of Fame rehearsals, induction and performance, 1993 January (Box 10, Object 7)
      - Royal Albert Hall, London, England, 2005 May 2-2005 May 6 (Box 10, Object 8-16)
      - Today; Cream: Royal Albert Hall DVD trailer, 2005 November 18, 2005 (Box 10, Object 17)
    - Creedence Clearwater Revival
      - Various including Johnny Cash Show, Ed Sullivan Show, Royal Albert Hall, 1969-1971 and undated (Box 10, Object 18-19)
      - Oakland, California; American Bandstand, 1969-1970 (Box 10, Object 20)
      - Overdrive rebroadcast, 1970 (Box 7, Object 142)
      - Compilation, undated (Box 10, Object 21)
    - Croce, Jim: Don Kirshner's Rock Concert Special, 1974 (Box 10, Object 22)
    - Crosby, Stills and Nash
      - Buffalo, New York, 1990 July 16 (Box 10, Object 23)
      - Various including Entertainment Tonight, VH-1 Storytellers with Neil Young, Woodstock '94, 1990-1994, 2000 (Box 10, Object 24-25)
      - NHK Arena, Tokyo, Japan, 1991 April 22 (Box 10, Object 26)
    - Crosby, Stills, Nash and Young
      - Wembley, 1974 (Box 10, Object 27)
      - VH1 Legends profile; Bridge Benefit, San Francisco, California, 1991 and undated (Box 10, Object 28)
    - Cult: Brixton Academy, England, 1987 (Box 10, Object 29)
    - Darin, Bobby: Darin Invasion with Linda Ronstadt, 1970 (Box 10, Object 30)
    - Deep Purple
      - Live in Denmark; Don Kirshner's Rock Concert, 1972-1973 (Box 10, Object 31)
      - California Jam; Rises Over Japan; press conference, 1974-1975, 1984 (Box 10, Object 32)
      - Deep Purple: Heavy Metal Pioneers, 1991 (Box 10, Object 33)
      - Vienna, Austria, 1996 (Box 10, Object 34)
    - Derek and the Dominos: Johnny Cash Show, undated (Box 8, Object 36)
    - Dire Straits
      - Various including Old Grey Whistle Test, Rockpalast, Studio L, Live Aid, Brothers in Arms concert, Wembly, London, England, 1978-1985, 1988 (Box 10, Object 35-37)
      - Rock Pop [filed with Stevie Ray Vaughan], 1980
      - Sydney, Australia, 1986 May 26 (Box 10, Object 38-39)
      - Israel; German television, 1986 (Box 10, Object 39)
      - Freedomfest -- Free Nelson Mandela Concert with Eric Clapton, Wembly Arena, London, England, 1988 June 11 (Box 10, Object 40-41)
      - Madison Square Garden, New York, New York, 1992 February 26 (Box 10, Object 42-43)
      - On Every Street, Nimes, France, 1992 May (Box 10, Object 43-44)
      - Basel, Switzerland, 1992 June 28 (Box 10, Object 45)
    - Divinyls: various including "Pleasure and Pain" and "Sleeping Beauty" promos, US Festival, MTV New Year's Bash, "Best of" promo compile, 1983-1991, undated (Box 10, Object 46-47)
    - Donovan: Soundstage, 1974 December 30 (Box 8, Object 36)
    - Doobie Brothers
      - French television, 1974 (Box 12, Object 52)
      - Winterland, San Francisco, California; Young Music Show, 1976 and undated (Box 10, Object 48)
      - Soundstage, 1977, 1979 (Box 10, Object 49)
      - Farewell concert, San Francisco, California, 1982 (Box 10, Object 50)
      - Best Hit USA; Honolulu, Hawaii; International Rock Music Awards, 1989-1991 (Box 10, Object 51)
    - Doors, 1968 (Box 10, Object 52)
    - Dylan, Bob
      - Last Waltz; Rolling Thunder Review Hard Rain" Tour, 1976 (Box 10, Object 53)
      - World of John Hammond; Late Night with David Letterman rehearsal, 1975, 1984 (Box 12, Object 47)
      - Hearts of Fire, 1987 (Box 10, Object 54)
      - Woodstock '94, 1994 August 14 (Box 10, Object 55)
      - Various including 60 Minutes, Tsunami Aid Concert, 60s Rock Experience, 2004-2005 (Box 10, Object 56)
    - Eagles
      - Various including BBC In Concert, Don Kirshner's Rock Concert, BBC Sounds the Seventies [ Old Grey Whistle Test], 1973-1974, 1998 and undated (Box 10, Object 57-58)
      - Kingdome, Seattle, Washington, 1976 June 7 (Box 10, Object 59)
      - When Hell Freezes Over, MTV concert broadcast, 1994 April (Box 10, Object 60)
      - "Farewell One" concert, Australia, 2005 (Box 10, Object 61)
    - Edmunds, David: Rockpalast, Loreley, Germany, 1983 (Box 10, Object 62)
    - Everly Brothers: Rock 'N' Roll Odyssey, 1984 (Box 10, Object 63)
    - Fabulous Thunderbirds: various including Rock-Pop, Austin Music Awards, Austin City Limits, 1980-1988 (Box 10, Object 64)
    - Faces: Pop-2 with Mick Jagger interview, 1971 January 26 (Box 13, Object 135)
    - Feist: Saturday Night Live, 2007 November 3 (Box 10, Object 65)
    - Firm: Hammersmith, Odeon, London, England, 1984 December (Box 10, Object 66)
    - Fleetwood Mac
      - Various including Beat Club, Midnight Special, California Jam II, 1968, undated (Box 10, Object 67)
      - Capitol Theater, Maryland, 1975 (Box 10, Object 68)
      - Forum, Los Angeles, California -- "Mirage Tour", 1982 (Box 10, Object 69)
      - Rock Steady; Going Home, 1991 February 14, 1993 (Box 10, Object 70)
    - Fogerty, John
      - Various including "All Stars" cable special; Vietnam Veterans Welcome Home Concert; Farm Aid; Roy Orbison Tribute to Benefit Homeless, 1985-1983, undated (Box 10, Object 71-73)
      - Rock and Roll Hall of Fame concert, Cleveland, Ohio; Premonition concert, Warner Brothers Studios, California, 1995 September 2, 1997 December (Box 10, Object 74)
      - Hammerstein Ballroom, New York, New York, 1997 June 2 (Box 10, Object 75)
      - Guvernment, Toronto, Canada, 1997 June 30 (Box 10, Object 76-77)
      - Hard Rock Live, 1997 August (Box 10, Object 77)
      - Various including VH-1 Storytellers, Late Night with David Letterman, VH-1 Legends, 1997 (Box 10, Object 78-79)
      - A&E Live by Request, 2004 September 22 (Box 10, Object 80)
      - Austin City Limits, 2004 October 2 (Box 10, Object 81-82)
    - Foghat: Rainbow Theater, London, England; Don Kirshner's Rock Concert; Hollywood, Florida, 1974-1977, 1981 (Box 10, Object 83)
    - Foreigner
      - Various including "California Jam II," Nurburgring, Germany; Atlantic Records 40th Anniversary, 1978, 1981-1988 (Box 10, Object 84)
      - Super Rock 1985, live in Japan (Box 10, Object 85)
      - Feels Like the First Time, 1991 (Box 10, Object 86)
    - Frampton, Peter: Sao Paulo, Brazil, 1980 (Box 10, Object 87)
    - Gallagher, Rory
      - Various including Beat Club, Marquee, London, England, Don Kirshner's Rock Concert, 1970-1975, undated (Box 10, Object 88)
      - Old Grey Whistle Test; Sight and Sounds at Hammersmith Odeon, 1976 March 2, 1977 January 29 (Box 10, Object 89)
      - Rockpalast; Montreux Jazz Festival; Aspects of Rock, 1976 June 9, 1979 (Box 10, Object 90)
      - Studio L, Cologne, Germany, 1976 June 10 (Box 10, Object 91)
      - Sight and Sound at Hammersmith Odeon, 1977 January 29 (Box 10, Object 92)
      - Grugahalle, Essen, Germany, 1977 July 23 (Box 10, Object 93)
      - Weisbaden Festival, Germany, 1979 May 6 (Box 10, Object 94)
      - Loreley, Germany, 1982 August 28 (Box 10, Object 95)
      - Loreley Jam, Germany with Eric Burdon and David Lindley, 1982 Augutst 28 (Box 10, Object 96)
      - Dinkelsbuhl, Germany; Stadtfestival, Vienna, Austria, 1986 July 5, 1987 May 2 (Box 10, Object 97)
      - "Messin' with the Kid," live at the Cork Opera House, 1990 (Box 10, Object 98)
      - Ohne Filter Extra, Baden Baden, Germany, 1990 (Box 10, Object 99)
      - Rocklife with Jack Bruce, 1990 (Box 10, Object 100)
    - Gilmour, David: in concert, conceptual videos and After the Floyd documentary; Guitar Greats concert; Saturday Night Live, 1984 (Box 10, Object 101)
    - Go-Go's
      - Metropol, Berlin, Germany, 1982 (Box 10, Object 101-102)
      - Peppermint Lounge, 1982 (Box 10, Object 102)
      - Dick Clark's New Year's Eve; Wild At the Greek; Prime Time, 1983-1984 (Box 10, Object 103)
    - Golden Earring: various including Top of the Pops; "Radar Love" promo film; Live from the Twilight Zone, 1973-1976, 1983 (Box 10, Object 104)
    - Grand Funk Railroad
      - Various including Texas Pop Festival and ABC In Concert, 1969-1973 (Box 10, Object 105)
      - Grand Funk Railroad - Live at L.A. Forum; VH-1 Legends, 1974, 1999 (Box 10, Object 106)
    - Green, Peter: Top of the Pops; Rockpalast; The Works, 1971-1982, 1996 (Box 10, Object 107)
    - Guess Who
      - "Together Again" reunion concert, 1983 (Box 10, Object 108)
      - Winnipeg, Manitoba, Canada with Neil Young; Molson Park, Barrie, Ontario, Canada with Bachman, Turner Overdrive, 1987-1988 (Box 10, Object 109)
    - Guy, Buddy: Our Lady of Fatima Church, Peabody, Massachusetts, 1991 May 24 (Box 10, Object 110)
    - Harrison, George and Eric Clapton
      - Various interviews and press conferences from 1991 tour of Japan, 1991 November (Box 10, Object 111)
      - Kanagowa Arena, Yokohama, Japan, 1991 December 1 (Box 10, Object 112, 119)
      - Hiroshima, Japan, 1991 December 6 (Box 10, Object 119)
      - Castle Hall ,Osaka, Japan, 1991 December 10 (Box 10, Object 113-119)
      - Tokyo Dome, Japan, 1991 December 14, 1991 December 17 (Box 10, Object 120-122)
    - Havens, Richie
      - Purely Music -- Ohne Filter Extra; Los Angeles, California, 1988, 1989 (Box 10, Object 123)
      - Bottom Line, New York, New York; New Orleans Jazz Festival; "Freedom" -- Best of Classic Rock, 1990 December 14, 1991 May 2 and undated (Box 10, Object 124)
    - Healey, Jeff
      - Various including "It's Only Rock 'N Roll" with Stevie Ray Vaughan and Halifax, Nova Scotia, 1987-1989 (Box 10, Object 125)
      - See the Light, London, England; Bonn, Germany with John Mayall, 1989 April 14, 1989 May 1 (Box 10, Object 126)
      - Various including Toronto Blues Festival, Arsenio Hall Show, Pistoia Blues Festival, Italy, 1989-1990, 1992 (Box 10, Object 127-128)
    - Heart
      - Second Ending, 1976 (Box 10, Object 129)
      - Various including Concert for the Americas, Dominican Republic and On the Road With Heart, 1982, 1986 (Box 10, Object 130)
      - Studio voiceover sessions for Heart and interviews, 1984 (Box 10, Object 131-132)
      - Ames, Iowa, 1987 (Box 10, Object 133)
      - Orange County, New York, 1988 June (Box 10, Object 134)
      - Hamilton, Ontario, Canada, 1988 (Box 10, Object 135)
    - Hendrix, Jimi
      - Various including Night Train, Lulu Show, Marquee Club, London, England, 1965, 1967-1969 (Box 10, Object 136)
      - Popside, 1967 (Box 10, Object 137)
      - Hendrix, Jimi: South Bank Show, 1989 (Box 10, Object 138)
      - Fillmore footage, undated (Box 14, Object 16)
    - Henley, Don: Tokyo Dome, Tokyo, Japan, 1989 December 31 (Box 10, Object 139)
    - Hot Tuna: Fillmore: The Last Days; Lonestar, New York, New York, 1972, 1991 (Box 10, Object 140)
    - Houston, Whitney: various including VH-1 and Yokohama, Japan, 1986-1990 (Box 10, Object 141)
    - J. Geils Band
      - Grugahalle, Essen, Germany, 1979 April 21 (Box 10, Object 142)
      - Rock-Pop In Concert; Live in Boston, 1980 (Box 10, Object 143)
    - Jaybirds: "Not Fade Away", undated (Box 10, Object 144)
    - Jefferson Airplane
      - Radio City Music Hall, New York, New York, 1989 August 29 (Box 10, Object 145-146)
      - Golden Gate Park, San Francisco, California, 1989 September 30 (Box 10, Object 147-148)
      - Various including Inside Track with Graham Nash, Howard Stern Show, Behind the Music, 1990, 1993, undated (Box 10, Object 149)
    - Jefferson Starship: Live; "What's Going On'; Super Night of Rock and Roll, 1983, undated (Box 10, Object 150)
    - Jethro Tull
      - Stockholm, Sweden, 1969 (Box 10, Object 137)
      - Too Old to Rock 'n' Roll; Top of the Pops; Sight and Sound, 1976 (Box 10, Object 151)
      - Various including Madison Square Garden, New York, New York and "Minstrel in the Gallery" promo, 1975, 1977-1978 (Box 10, Object 152)
      - Storm Watch; Royal Albert Hall, London, England; Hammersmith Odeon, London, England, 1980 (Box 10, Object 153)
      - Ohne Maulkorb, Olympiahalle, Germany; Rock-Pop In Concert, 19801981 (Box 10, Object 154)
      - Seven Up Theater, Rome, Italy; Live in Rome, 1982 (Box 11, Object 1)
      - Various including Dortmund, Germany, Late Night with David Lettermen, Rock and Classic, 1982-1983 (Box 11, Object 2)
      - Berlin, Germany [soundcheck]; Tribute to Bach; Out in the Green, 1985-1986 (Box 11, Object 3)
      - Fish 'n' Sheep and Rock 'n' Roll; MTV Rock Influences: Progressive Rock; hosting MTV, 1986-1987 (Box 11, Object 4)
      - Detroit, Michigan, 1987 November 27 (Box 11, Object 5)
      - "Steel Monkeys" promo and interview; Maple Leaf Gardens, Toronto, Canada, 1987, 1988 November 19 (Box 11, Object 6)
      - New England College interview; "20 Years Tour," Vienna, Austria, 1988 (Box 11, Object 7)
      - King's Dominion Showplace, Doswell, Virginia, 1988 July 19 (Box 11, Object 8)
      - Brazil interview; Ibirapuera, Sao Paulo, Brazil, 1988 (Box 11, Object 9)
      - Porto Allegre, Brazil, 1988 August (Box 11, Object 10)
      - Shoreline Amphitheater, Mountainview, California, 1988 (Box 11, Object 11)
      - Essen, Germany [private], 1989 October 9 (Box 11, Object 12)
      - New Haven, Connecticut, 1989 October 31 (Box 11, Object 13)
      - Nottingham, England, 1990 May 21 (Box 11, Object 14-15)
      - AM-TV interview [UK], 1990 June 25 (Box 11, Object 15)
      - Ibirapuera, Sao Paulo, Brazil, 1990 September 15 (Box 11, Object 16)
      - Milano, Italy [private], 1991 January 13 (Box 11, Object 17)
      - Grugahalle, Essen, Germany, 1991 October 21 (Box 11, Object 18-19)
      - David Letterman Show and rehearsal, 1991 August 20 (Box 11, Object 19)
      - Beacon Theatre, New York, New York, 1992 October 5 (Box 11, Object 20)
    - Jett, Joan, and the Blackhearts: Westfallenhalle, Dortmund, Germany, 1982 (Box 11, Object 21)
    - Jimmy Cliff's All-Stars: Woodstock '94, 1994 (Box 12, Object 58)
    - Johnson, Eric: Austin City Limits; Bottom Line, New York, New York, 1989, 1990 July 20 (Box 11, Object 22)
    - Joplin, Janis: Swedish television, undated (Box 10, Object 137)
    - Kansas: Omaha, Nebraska, 1982 June (Box 11, Object 23)
    - Katrina and the Waves: Walking on Sunshine; Zeche, Bochum, Germany, 1985 (Box 11, Object 24)
    - King, Albert
      - Maintenance Shop Blues, Iowa, 1981 (Box 11, Object 25)
      - Harbourfront, Toronto, Canada, 1987 July 5 (Box 11, Object 26)
      - Montreux Jazz Festival; Ohne Filter Extra, 1990, 1992 November 11 (Box 11, Object 27)
    - King, B.B.
      - Austin City Limits; Live At Nick's, 1982-1983 (Box 11, Object 28)
      - In Session with Larry Carlton; Theater Fabrik, Hamburg, Germany, 1985, 1986 October 28 (Box 11, Object 29)
      - The Tube; Hotel National, Rio De Janeiro, Brazil, 1986 (Box 11, Object 30)
      - Montreux Jazz Festival; Omnibus; Yesterday Special, 1990 and undated (Box 11, Object 31)
    - King, Freddie
      - The !!!! Beat; Sweden, 1966, 1973 (Box 11, Object 32)
      - Sugar Bowl, Charlotte, North Carolina, 1972 (Box 11, Object 33)
      - Dallas, Texas, 1973 January 20 (Box 11, Object 34)
    - Kinks
      - Grugahalle, Essen, Germany, 1982 March 4 (Box 11, Object 35)
      - Story of the Kinks; VH-1 profile; Festhalle, Frankfurt, Germany, 1984, 1990 and undated (Box 11, Object 36)
      - Massey Hall, Toronto, Canada, 1988 (Box 11, Object 37)
    - Kooper, Al: Steve Paul's Scene with Blues Project; Bottom Line, New York, New York, 1966, 1990 (Box 11, Object 38)
    - Kottke, Leo: Bottom Line, New York, New York, 1990 February 19 (Box 11, Object 39)
    - Led Zeppelin
      - Knebworth Festival, England with promos, 1979 August 11 (Box 11, Object 40-41)
      - Denmark, 1969 (Box 10, Object 52)
      - Various including Live Aid, Atlantic Records 40th Anniversary, American Music Awards, "Unledded - MTV Unplugged [Page and Plant], 1985, 1988-1997 (Box 11, Object 42-44)
    - Lee, Alvin / Alvin Lee Band
      - Home movies including Ten Years After 1970 U.S. tour and Ten Years Later concert footage, 1970, undated (Box 11, Object 45)
      - Pump Iron promos; Jukebox with FBI, Faces, Keith Richards, and Rainbow, 1975 (Box 11, Object 46)
      - Various including Yesterday Special, Gas Tank, Night of the Guitar, Power Play, 1983-1994 (Box 11, Object 47-51)
      - Nurnberg, Germany; Gmunden, Austria; Munich, Germany, 1984 February 17-1984 February 21 (Box 11, Object 52)
      - Genoa, Italy, 1984 March 24 (Box 11, Object 53)
      - Vienna, Austria; Postof-Linz, Austria, 1984 April 1, 1987 (Box 11, Object 54)
      - Alabamahalle, Munich, Germany, 1984 December 7 (Box 11, Object 55)
      - Stuttgart, Germany, 1984 December 8 (Box 11, Object 56)
      - Various including Munich, Germany and Stuttgart, Germany, 1984-1986 (Box 11, Object 57-58)
      - Theater Fabrik, Munich, Germany; Nurnberg, Germany; Vienna, Austria, 1984-1985 (Box 11, Object 59)
      - Jurahalle, Neumarkt, Germany, 1986 May 16 (Box 11, Object 60)
      - Zeche, Bochum, Germany, 1986 May 19 (Box 11, Object 61)
      - Metropol, Vienna, Austria, 1987 January 29 (Box 11, Object 62)
      - Brat Stop, Kenosha, Wisconsin, 1987 April 9 (Box 11, Object 63)
      - Stadtfest, Vienna, Austria, 1987 May 2 (Box 11, Object 64-66)
      - Donauinsel, Vienna, Austria, 1992 June 28 (Box 11, Object 67-68)
      - Burghausen, Germany; Augsburg, Germany, 1992 October 3, 1993 July 17 (Box 11, Object 69)
      - Rockhaus, Vienna, Austria, 1992 October 18 (Box 11, Object 70)
      - RTL-TV -- "Little Bit of Love", 1992 (Box 12, Object 112)
      - Beim Festival, Karlsruhe, Germany, 1993 August (Box 11, Object 71)
      - Regensburg, Germany, 1994 January 22 (Box 11, Object 72)
      - Ohne Filter Extra, Baden Baden, Germany and interview, 1994 April 18 (Box 11, Object 73-74)
      - Rockhaus, Vienna, Austria, 1994 June 16 (Box 11, Object 75)
      - Rolling Thunder Festival, Munich, Germany, 1994 August 26 (Box 11, Object 76)
      - Coach House, San Juan Capistrano, California with Nine Below Zero, 1994 November 6 (Box 11, Object 77)
      - Youth Hall, Moscow, Russia, 1995 March 25 (Box 11, Object 78)
      - Posthof-Linz, Austria, 1995 September 30, 1997 March 22 (Box 11, Object 79)
      - Santerhalle, Wartberg-Krems, Austria, 1996 June 22 (Box 11, Object 80)
      - Sporthalle, Saarbrucken, Germany, 1997 April 30 (Box 11, Object 81)
      - Erfurt, Germany, 2001 April 6 (Box 11, Object 82)
      - Blues festival, Nurnberg, Germany, 2001 April 7 (Box 11, Object 83)
    - Lennon, John, and Yoko Ono, Mike Douglas Show, 1972 February 14-1972 February 18 (Box 11, Object 84-85)
    - Little Feat: various including Old Grey Whistle Test. Grugahalle, Essen Germany, New Orleans Jazz Festival, 1975-1977, 1990, undated (Box 11, Object 86)
    - Lone Justice: various including Palomino Club, Hollywood, California and Ritz, New York, New York, 1983-1987 (Box 11, Object 87)
    - Los Lobos
      - Various including Rock & Roll Palace, Los Angeles, California, Spectrum, Montreal, Canada, Austin City Limits, 1984-1987 (Box 11, Object 88-89)
      - Japanese tour, 1988 (Box 11, Object 90)
      - Lonesome Pine, 1993 February 7 (Box 11, Object 91)
    - Lynyrd Skynyrd
      - Various including Goldenn Age of Rock and Roll, Rockpalast, Knebworth Festival, England, 1974-1976 (Box 11, Object 92)
      - Old Grey Whistle Test; Winterland, San Francisco, California, 1975 November 11, 1976 March 7 (Box 11, Object 93)
      - Tribute tour, 1988 (Box 11, Object 94)
    - Mamas and the Papas: California Dreamin', undated (Box 11, Object 95)
    - Marriott, Steve
      - Carolina Jam, Summerville, South Carolina, 1983 (Box 11, Object 96)
      - Parkzidat, Rotterdam, Holland; "I Don't Need No Doctor", 1985 December 13 and undated (Box 11, Object 97)
    - Marshall Tucker Band: Then and Now, undated (Box 11, Object 98)
    - Mason, Dave
      - Soundstage, 1974 December 30 (Box 8, Object 36)
      - Chicago, Illinois with Spencer Davis, 1989 July 14 (Box 11, Object 99)
      - Mielpaque Hall, Tokyo, Japan, 1991 June 24 (Box 11, Object 100)
    - Mayall, John
      - Viareggio, Italy; Ames, Iowa, 1983, 1985 (Box 11, Object 101)
      - Vienna, Austria, 1987 March 22 (Box 11, Object 102)
      - Kosmos, Berlin, Germany with Coco Montoya and Walter Trout, 1987 May 4 (Box 11, Object 103)
      - Bonn, Germany with Jeff Healey; Bayou Club, Washington, D.C.; Sacramento, California, 1988, undated (Box 11, Object 104)
      - Rock History; Much Music; Utah Blues Festival, 1989-1990 (Box 11, Object 105)
      - Bottom Line, New York, New York; Tonight Show Starring Johnny Carson, 1990 June 1, 1991 February 8 (Box 11, Object 106)
      - Rock Steady; Austin City Limits, 1991 February 19, 1994 (Box 11, Object 107)
    - McCartney, Paul
      - James Paul McCartney; One Hand Clapping, 1973-1974 (Box 11, Object 108)
      - Rock Show, Kingdome, Seattle, Washington with Wings, 1976 (Box 11, Object 109)
      - Los Angeles, California, 1989 November 29 (Box 11, Object 110)
      - Madison Square Garden, New York, New York, 1989 December 12 (Box 11, Object 111-112)
      - Get Back, 1989 (Box 11, Object 112)
      - Put it There; Lyceum, New York, 1989 (Box 11, Object 113)
      - Tokyo, Japan, 1990 March 9 (Box 11, Object 114)
      - Various including Knebworth Festival, MTV Rockumentary, MTV Unplugged [Japanese television], 1990-1991 (Box 11, Object 115)
      - MTV Unplugged [complete session], 1990 (Box 11, Object 116)